Dick Russell papers, Inclusive: 1924-2011, undated, Bulk: 1964-2003, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Subject Files, 1960-2011, undated; 4
  - Domestic Spying, Cops, Military, IRS, 1970-1975 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Domestic Spying, Cops, Military, IRS, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Domestic Spying, Cops, Military, IRS, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Domestic Spying, Cops, Military, IRS, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Domestic Spying, Cops, Military, IRS, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Early American History, News Clippings, undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - East German Spying, KGB (1 of 2), 1993-1999 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - East German Spying, KGB (1 of 2), 1993-1999 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings, 1977-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings (1 of 5), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings (2 of 5), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings (3 of 5), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings (4 of 5), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings (5 of 5), 1995 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Far Right Extremist, News Clippings, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - FBI, News Clippings, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - FBI, News Clippings, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses (1 of 2), undated (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses (2 of 2), undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - FBI, Kelley, Clarence, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - FBI, Domestic Abuses, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Great Depression,1930’s, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Great Depression,1930’s, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Great Depression,1930’s, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Great Depression,1930’s, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Great Depression,1930’s, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Great Depression,1930’s, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Great Depression,1930’s, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Gulf War Syndrome, News Clippings, 1993-2000 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Hitler and Nazi Germany, News Clippings, undated (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), de Mohnrenschildt, George, Report, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), de Mohnrenschildt, George, General, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), de Mohnrenschildt, George, Testimony, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Mexico City Report (1 of 3), 1993 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Mexico City Report (2 of 3), 1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Mexico City Report (3 of 3), 1993 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Hughes, Howard, Will, News Clippings, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Hughes, Howard, Will, News Clippings, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Hughes, Howard, Will, News Clippings, 1981 and 1988 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Hughes, Howard, Will, News Clippings, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Interpol, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Interpol, Dickoff, Paul, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Interpol, General, 1974-1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Interpol, Report, “The International Criminal Police Organization (Interpol): A Documented History”, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Interpol, Report, “Interpol: A Synopsis”, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Iran Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, News Clippings, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Bush Era (1 of 2), undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Bush Era (2 of 2), undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Bush Era, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Bush Era, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Bush Era, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Bush Era, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Bush Era, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Drugs/Noriega, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Drugs/Noriega, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Drugs/Noriega, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Drugs/Noriega, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Iran-Contra Scandal, Book, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Iraq-gate, News Clippings, 1990-1996 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Lockheed Scandals, News Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, News Clippings, 1978-1983 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, News Clippings, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, News Clippings, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, News Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, News Clippings, 1986-2002 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, News Clippings, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, Article, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, Article, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, Orders to Kill, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, Persons of Interest, 1969; undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Assassination, PROBE Magazine, 1998,1999 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Civil Rights Movement, 1983-2000 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Conferences, Pilgrimage to Memphis, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Conferences, Three Decades of Doubt, General, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Conferences, Three Decades of Doubt, Sessions, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Conferences, Three Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), Decades of Doubt, Joe Brown, Jr., 1998 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Article, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Contract, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Notes, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Research, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Research, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Research (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), High Times Magazine, Research (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), King Case, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), James Earl Ray, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK), John Larry Ray, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Mob, News Clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Mob, News Clippings, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Mob, News Clippings, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Mob, News Clippings, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Mob, News Clippings, 1981-1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Mob, News Clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Mob, News Clippings, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (1 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (2 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (3 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (4 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (5 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (6 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (7 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (8 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (9 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (10 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (11 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (12 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (13 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (14 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (15 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Richard Nagell, Army Intelligence/Secret Service (16 of 16), 1964-1993 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Richard Nagell, CIA, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Richard Nagell, JFK Lancer Publication, 1993-1995 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Richard Nagell, Researchers Correspondence, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Richard Nagell, Secret Service (1 of 4), 1963-1998 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Richard Nagell, Secret Service (2 of 4), 1963-1998 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Richard Nagell, Secret Service (3 of 4), 1963-1998 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Richard Nagell, Secret Service (4 of 4), 1963-1998 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Nazi Gold/ WWII, News Clippings, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - N.S.A., 1986 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Cudlaty, Frank, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Ekdahl, Edwin, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Film Records, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Gilbert, Samuel, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Kurian, Milton, 1964; 1998 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Landersburg, Steven Harris, 1994-1997 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Marguerite, Oswald, 1994-1996 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Markham, James, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, New Orleans, 1994-1997 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Notes, undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Paine, Ruth, undated (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Presentation, 1994-1997 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, PROBE Articles, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Research Requests, 1995-1997 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Tippet Shooting, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Two Oswalds, Two Families, 1994-1997 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Two Oswalds Research, 1994-1997 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Youth & Education, Chronology, 1994-1997 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Oswald, John Armstrong Material, Youth & Education, General, 1994-1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Oswald, Autopsy, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Oswald, Chronology (1 of 2), 1924-1963 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Oswald, Chronology (2 of 2), 1924-1963 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Oswald, Confidential Informants, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Articles & Book Excerpts, 1975-1995 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Birth Certificates, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Brown, Verna Deane, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Commission Exhibit, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Ellsworth, Frank, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, General, 1974-1985 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Hansen, John, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Holcombe, A.D., 1967 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, House, Donald Wayne, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Notes, 1995-1997 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Oswald, Marguerite, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Price, C.J., 1964 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Oswald, Double Oswald, Statements, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Oswald, New Orleans Public Library, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Oswald, U.S.S.R., 1959-1970 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Presidents, General, 1978-1988 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Presidents, Bush Family General, 1988-1999 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Presidents, Carter (1 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Presidents, Carter (2 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Presidents, Clinton Administration, 1993-2000 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1997 January (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1997 February (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1997 March (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1997 April-June (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1997 July-September (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1997 October (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1997 November-December (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1998 January-April (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1998 May-August (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1998 September-December (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Presidents, Clinton Whitewater, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Presidents, Ford, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Presidents, Ford, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Presidents, Johnson (LBJ), Vietnam, 1995-1999 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Presidents, Nixon, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Presidents, Nixon, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Bahamas, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Bahamas, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Rebozo, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Tax, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Tax, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Teamster, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate-10 years later, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate-10 years later, News Clippings, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate-10 years later, Notes, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate-10 years later, Players, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate-10 years later, Drafts, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate-Bay of Pigs Link, undated (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate, Money Chain, Articles, 1973, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate, Money Chain, Arthur Schwartz, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate, Money Chain, Case Studies, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate, Money Chain, Money and Investors, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Presidents, Nixon, Watergate-Mysterious Deaths, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Presidents, Nixon, New Tapes, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Presidents, Nixon and the Dallas Republicans, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Presidents, Nixon, William Casey, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Presidents, Nixon, William Casey, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Presidents, Nixon, William Casey, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Friends, 1983-1985 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Friends, 1980-1983 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Friends, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Presidents, Reagan and Government, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 1981 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 1988-1990 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 1998-1999 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Presidents, Roosevelt (FDR), undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Presidents, Truman/Eisenhower +1950’s Cold War, 1978-2000 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Privacy, Articles, 1977-1984 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Privacy, Articles, “Is Privacy Dead?” By Dick Russell, undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Privacy, Computer Issues, 1993-2000 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Privacy, Federal Trade Commission, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Privacy, News Clips, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Privacy, News Clips, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Privacy, News Clips, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Privacy, News Clips, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 23)